// Questions for the quiz
const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which is the WRONG way to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        options: ["let", "const", "var", "def"],
        answer: "def",
    },
    {
        question: "How can JavaScript access an element on a page?",
        options: [
            "document.querySelector()",
            "document.fetchID()",
            "document.getItem()",
            "document.element()",
        ],
        answer: "document.querySelector()",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the proper format for a for loop?",
        options: [
            "for (let i = 0. i++. i < item.length)",
            "for (let i = 0; i < item.length; i++)",
            "for ({let i = 0}, {i < item.length}, {i++})",
            "for (item[length]; i++; let i = 0)",
        ],
        answer: "for (let i = 0; i < item.length; i++)",
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which character correctly follows a variable declaration in JavaScript?",
        options: ["Semi colon", "colon", "period", "curly brace"],
        answer: "Semi colon",
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which of the following is one way to reference a property of an object?",
        options: ["object.name", "object/name", "object-name", "object~name"],
        answer: "object.name",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a primitive data type?",
        options: ["number/int", "string", "boolean", "hexcode"],
        answer: "hexcode",
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of data does JSON read?",
        options: ["objects", "arrays", "strings", "loops"],
        answer: "strings",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the variable declarations are not mutable?",
        options: ["x = 32", "const y = 45", "let z = 24", "var a = 75"],
        answer: "const y = 45",
    },
    {
        question: "How do you print data to the console in the browser?",
        options: [
            "print(data)",
            "display(data)",
            "console.show(data)",
            "console.log(data)",
        ],
        answer: "console.log(data)",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the creator of JavaScript?",
        options: [
            "Bill Gates",
            "Zima Juliapos",
            "Brendan Eich",
            "Mark Zuckerberg",
        ],
        answer: "Brendan Eich",
    },
];
